<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bios on CircleCityCon 7.0</title>
    <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bios on CircleCityCon 7.0</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://circlecitycon.com/bios/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Sawyer</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/aaron_sawyer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/aaron_sawyer/</guid>
      <description>Aaron Sawyer is an intern at InfoSec Innovations and post-baccalaureate student at the University of Maine. Between stints as a laboratory technician in an Astroparticle Physics Laboratory, Aaron worked as a Merchant Marine Engineer where he became a certified vessel security officer and discovered his love of breaking things in interesting ways.
 talk Catching the Guerrilla: Powershell Counterinsurgency  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Scantlin</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/aaron_scantlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/aaron_scantlin/</guid>
      <description>Aaron holds specialized certifications from the SysAdmin, Audit, Network and Security (SANS) Institute and has spoken at numerous security conferences and meetups. He currently serves as vice president of the central Missouri chapter of Infragard, a partnership between the private sector and the FBI dedicated to sharing information and intelligence to prevent hostile acts against the United States. At the University of Missouri, Aaron serves as a security analyst for the central information technology division and he teaches the Electrical Engineering and Computer Science Department’s cyber security course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adi Ikan</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/adi_ikan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/adi_ikan/</guid>
      <description>Cyber Security Research Team Leader at Check Point Software Technologies. Prior to Check Point, I have served as an Officer in the IDF Intelligence Corps 8200 Unit in various research and development roles. In addition, I Hold an M.Sc. in Financial Mathematics and a B.Sc. in Applied Mathematics at Bar-Ilan University.
 talk Nexus Zeta - How a newbie hacker managed to create a monster botnet  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alex Chalmers</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/alex_chalmers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/alex_chalmers/</guid>
      <description>Alex B Chalmers is a technical service manager for federated identity solutions at Eli Lilly and Company. He has served in a variety of senior technical roles across identity, security, and enterprise technology architecture over more than 15 years. Currently, his focus is the continuous improvement of cloud identity solutions and the broad adoption of strong authentication technologies. In addition to his technical roles, Alex has served as a university instructor in information security and provided technical training in a variety of cloud technology solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alyssa Miller</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/alyssa_miller/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/alyssa_miller/</guid>
      <description>Alyssa is a former developer turned pen-tester and security evangelist with over 15 years of experience in the security industry. She has maintained a heavy focus on application security over the years, not only conducting application assessments, threat modeling exercises and secure code reviews, but also working with companies to develop comprehensive secure SDLC programs. Alyssa is also experienced in delivering security training at all levels from basic awareness to detailed secure coding practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aman Sachdev</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/aman_sachdev/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/aman_sachdev/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amber Welch</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/amber_welch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/amber_welch/</guid>
      <description>Until she’s accepted for a Mars mission, Amber’s goal is to advance data protection and personal information privacy as a Privacy Technical Lead for Schellman &amp;amp; Company. Amber been assessing corporate privacy compliance programs for the past year and prior to that, managed security and privacy governance for a suite of SaaS products. She has previously worked in companies creating ERP, CRM, event planning, and biologics manufacturing software.
 talk Data Access Rights Exploits under New Privacy Laws  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April Wright</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/april_wright/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/april_wright/</guid>
      <description>April C. Wright is a hacker, O’Reilly author, teacher, and community leader who has been breaking, making, fixing, and defending the security of global critical communications and connections for over 25 years. She is an international speaker and trainer, educating and advising on matters of privacy and information security with the goal of safeguarding the digital components we rely on every day. April has held roles on defensive, operational, adversarial, and development teams throughout her career, and has spoken and contributed to numerous worldwide security conferences including BlackHat, DEF CON USA and DEF CON China, DerbyCon, Hack in Paris, DefCamp Romania, ITWeb South Africa, as well as for the US Government and industry organizations such as OWASP and ISSA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arden Meyer</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/arden_meyer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/arden_meyer/</guid>
      <description>Arden began his journey into IT in 1982 when he first learned to program computers, then quickly moved on to hacking BBS, PBX, and ICS systems. He joined the USAF in 1996 and for 15 years traveled the world doing various mysterious things with electrons. Arden was hand selected in the initial cadre of the Network Warfare Operations career field and tasked to develop the first Cyber Functional Training Unit where over the next three years he taught thousands of students everything from vulnerabilities in LMR/ICS/SS7 to basic computer programming to advanced exploitation &amp;amp; covert exfiltration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ashley Benitez Smith</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/ashley_benitez_smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/ashley_benitez_smith/</guid>
      <description>Ashley Benitez Smith is in her seventh year of teaching middle school in Maryland. She has been teaching Career and Technology Education classes for five years and likes her job most days. Ashley wishes to bring security into STEM curricula to inspire the next generation of security professionals. She also wants to educate students about security to prepare them for an ever changing digital landscape. Ashley has attended a few security conferences and has helped with events at Defcon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carl Hertz</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/carl_hertz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/carl_hertz/</guid>
      <description>Carl Hertz is Director of Information Technology at Elevate Energy, a non-profit dedicated to bringing the benefits of the Green Economy to everyone. He has been an IT professional for 30 years, a security professional for 15, a hiring manager for 20 years, a project manager for 10 years, and a goofball for all of his life. You can follow his posts about tech, security, music, cycling, astronomy, feminism, parenthood, depression, and all the lulz at @cillic on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catherine Ullman</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/catherine_ullman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/catherine_ullman/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Catherine J. Ullman is a security researcher, speaker, and Senior Information Security Analyst at University at Buffalo with over 20 years of highly technical experience. In her current role, Cathy is a data forensics and incident response (DFIR) specialist, performing incident management, intrusion detection, investigative services, and personnel case resolution in a dynamic academic environment. She additionally builds security awareness amongst faculty and staff via a comprehensive department-wide program which educates and informs users about how to prevent and detect social engineering threats, and how to compute and digitally communicate safely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chad Calease</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/chad_calease/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/chad_calease/</guid>
      <description>Chad&amp;rsquo;s experience and fluency in technology spans over 15 years, crosses sectors and contexts, including regulated industries like healthcare, transportation, and financial services, to marketing and advertising, education, and non-profit. His Twitter bio sums him up well: Dad, ludic, neurodivergent, grateful for many gifts. Mom said, &amp;ldquo;There&amp;rsquo;s always one weirdo on every bus.&amp;rdquo; But I can never find them.
 talk A Few Things Right: Insights from Live and Simulated Incident Response  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Roberts</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/chris_roberts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/chris_roberts/</guid>
      <description>Chris is currently the CSS for Attivo Networks, and is working on a number of projects within the deception and services space. Over the years, he&amp;rsquo;s founded or worked with a number of companies specializing in DarkNet research, intelligence gathering, cryptography, deception technologies, and providers of security services and threat intelligence.
Since the late 90’s Chris has been deeply involved with security R&amp;amp;D, consulting, and advisory services in his quest to protect and defend businesses and individuals against cyber attack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christian Bobadilla</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/christian_bobadilla/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/christian_bobadilla/</guid>
      <description>Christian was born and raised in Chile. He started working in the field of information security in 2007 while in Santiago, and moved to the United States in 2011. For the past 3 years, he has been working as a Principal Security Engineer at Priceline.com. He is a man of many hobbies including running, table tennis, soccer, magic tricks and photography.
 talk Behind The Locked Door: we built an escape room for security awareness  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christian Burrows</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/christian_burrows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/christian_burrows/</guid>
      <description>Christian Burrows is a security practitioner from Austin, TX . He has 7+ years of experience in blue team / security incident response for various software companies. Some of his work includes helping to save the internet from really bad 0-days that were successfully used against companies he has worked for, spending entirely too much cumulative time in Splunk, reversing game hacks, and always trying to find bad stuff in prod environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cindy Jones</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/cindy_jones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/cindy_jones/</guid>
      <description>Cindy Cindy Jones brings over 17 years of specialized IT and security experience to her role of Senior Security Consultant with Rapid7. Cindy maintains a CISSP and MCP certifications. She has worked in several arenas including Federal government, with the Department of Defense, education, technology and healthcare, with a focus on the development, maintenance and management of information security programs. Cindy is actively involved within the information security community and volunteers her time leading the registration team for BSides Las Vegas, volunteers for DerbyCon, is a Def Con Goon and holds a position on the board for BSides Texas and is an active volunteer for these local events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colin Campbell</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/colin_campbell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/colin_campbell/</guid>
      <description>Colin has been working in IT for more than 24 years, and has been with his current employer for 12 years. Not long after starting there, he had the obsolete corporate Disaster Recovery plan dumped in his lap and had to create a new, functional testing plan from it&amp;rsquo;s ashes. Under his direction, the DR plan has been tested annually and used operationally twice due to power failures and fires at the corporate HQ that shutdown operations in that location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cubed Wombat</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/cubed_wombat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/cubed_wombat/</guid>
      <description>Cubed Wombat has over 12 years of cybersecurity experience, most of which in finding malicious activity. Currently running a hunt team in a large enterprise environment.
Jabbo often makes CISOs weep with his pentest findings and runs purple team activity for Cubed&amp;rsquo;s team.
 training Sysmon Swimming Lessons for SOC folk and Hunt teams. AKA How not to drown in the deep end of the Windows internals enterprise ocean.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dan Beavin</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/dan_beavin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/dan_beavin/</guid>
      <description>Dan is currently a Senior Cybersecurity Engineer at Indiana University Health in Indianapolis. Dan has 7 years of experience focusing on security research, offensive security activities, incident response, and malware research. During his career Dan has been the project lead and manager of several different security implementations ranging from policies and procedures to the technical implementations of many different products. His current project is helping to build a mature red team for Indiana University Health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Danny Akacki</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/danny_akacki/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/danny_akacki/</guid>
      <description>rand0h is just a guy that loves to tell stories &amp;amp; lives for the community that surrounds him. He believes none of this is worth anything if we don&amp;rsquo;t put a premium on tribal knowledge share. That&amp;rsquo;s really all that matters.
 talk InfoSuck: The Nasty Bits Of The Industry We Want To Tell Noobs But Aren&amp;rsquo;t Allowed To In Polite Company.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dhiraj Mishra</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/dhiraj_mishra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/dhiraj_mishra/</guid>
      <description>Dhiraj Mishra is an active speaker and a bug hunter, discovered multiple zero days in modern web browsers, Metasploit Contributor. His work has been published on TheHackerNews, TheRegister, ZDNet &amp;amp; BleepingComputer.
 talk Call Of Duty, Modernest Browser Warfare v2  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doug &#34;c00p3r&#34; Copeland</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/doug_c00p3r_copeland/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/doug_c00p3r_copeland/</guid>
      <description>Bio: c00p3r has a background in varied tech support and security roles which have provided him experience in Linux, Mac and Windows environments. His own entry to the ‘cyborg’ Biohacker culture has been by augmenting his body with both NFC and RFID chips through ‘Dangerous Things’ products which were available at the BdyHaxCon in Austin, TX. His curiosity about the technology has led him to found the Dangerous Minds Podcast which has become a vehicle to dig deeper into the subjects of biohacking, grinding, implantable technology, locksport, and network security by interviewing leaders in these fields and learning from their experience, for more information about this go to www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fletcher Heisler</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/fletcher_heisler/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/fletcher_heisler/</guid>
      <description>Fletcher is the founder and CEO of Hunter2, a company that provides engineering teams with modern appsec training that isn&amp;rsquo;t lame; through an online platform of interactive labs, developers get hands-on practice exploiting and patching up real applications. Fletcher previously ran Real Python, an online community of hundreds of thousands learning modern web development and programming practices.
 training Offensive Python: Custom scripts for pentests
 talk Modern AppSec Gotchas</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gabrielle Hempel</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/gabrielle_hempel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/gabrielle_hempel/</guid>
      <description>Gabrielle E. Hempel, B.A., B.S. Gabrielle is a graduate of the University of Cincinnati, where she studied Neuroscience and Psychology. She worked for Advarra Institutional Review Board in regulatory pharmaceutical and medical device compliance, and led specialized committees targeting Phase I research and emergency research. She moved to IT consulting in 2018, and currently works as an Information Security Analyst with Accenture while pursuing a certificate in Advanced Computer Security at Stanford.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glytch Tech</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/glytch_tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/glytch_tech/</guid>
      <description>Glytch has been referred to as a real life MacGyver, making, breaking, (and fixing!) drones, robots, and other bits for over a decade. He’s designed and built dozens of 3d printed drones in various shapes and sizes. He focuses on optimizing and explaining the technologies underlying these projects to be human understandable, the results of which are viewable via his YouTube channel. He’s built projects such as Project Cuckoo, a drone for carrying a Hak5 WiFi Pineapple; General Chaos, a battlebot platform for serving mountain dew or launching rockets; a Wrench mask which tracks and displays the wearer’s eye expressions in real-time; deodorant-launching air cannons; an electric motorcycle using repurposed car parts; high performance computing rigs; as well as occasional repair and self sufficiency related videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Himanshu Sharma</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/himanshu_sharma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/himanshu_sharma/</guid>
      <description>Himanshu Sharma (Co-Trainer): Himanshu Sharma, has been in the field of bug bounty since 2009 and has been listed in Apple, Google, Microsoft, Facebook, Adobe, Uber, AT&amp;amp;T, Avira, and many more with hall of fame listings as proofs. . He has helped celebrities such as Harbhajan Singh in recovering their hacked accounts, and also assisted an international singer in tracking down his hacked account and recovering it. He has been a speaker at multiple international conferences Botconf &amp;lsquo;13, Confidence 2018 and RSA Asia Pacific and Japan &amp;lsquo;18 .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jared Peck</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/jared_peck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/jared_peck/</guid>
      <description>Jared Peck is a threat intelligence analyst in the financial services industry. After some 15 years as a firefighter / paramedic, he turned his computer hobby into a profession. He worked his way from network administrator to being part of a SOC and now he does threat intelligence and attack detection development for a Fortune 500 company.
 talk F! Attribution  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jason Smith</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/jason_smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/jason_smith/</guid>
      <description>Self Taught Full Stack Developer, Code Louisville Mentor, and InfoSec Generalist. I love helping others with everything technology and am passionate about getting kids coding, hacking, tinkering and thinking about technology as a means to positively impacting the world around them. My son has fully embraced the Con life with me and begun his own self-learning journey and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t be happier!
 talk How to reach and teach youth about Cybersecurity (if anybody will let you)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jayson Brown</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/jayson_brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/jayson_brown/</guid>
      <description>Jayson Brown has been an IT jobber since the late 90&amp;rsquo;s. His knowledge is vast and deep when it comes to IT security. If you&amp;rsquo;ve seen it, he’s probably built it, hacked it and secured it. In his spare time, he designs artisan punch cards for his in-house Mainframe that he uses to hack all the things. His current work allows him to yell at security analysts about the differences between NAT and port forwarding and securing enterprise level business operations as an Internal Penetration Tester.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeff Man</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/jeff_man/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/jeff_man/</guid>
      <description>Respected Information Security expert, advisor, evangelist, co-host on Paul&amp;rsquo;s Security Weekly, and recently returned to a Consulting/Advisory role at Online Business Systems. Over 35 years of experience working in all aspects of computer, network, and information security, including risk management, vulnerability analysis, compliance assessment, forensic analysis and penetration testing. Previously held security research, management and product development roles with the National Security Agency, the DoD and private-sector enterprises and was part of the first penetration testing &amp;ldquo;red team&amp;rdquo; at NSA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Johnny Xmas</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/johnny_xmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/johnny_xmas/</guid>
      <description>Johnny Xmas is a predominant personality in the Information Security community, most well-known for his work on the TSA Master Key leaks between 2014 and 2018. Currently working with the Australian firm ‘Kasada’ to defend against the automated abuse of web infrastructure, he was previously the lead consultant on Uptake’s Industrial Cybersecurity Platform. Prior to this, he spent many years in the field as a penetration tester, focusing heavily on both IT and physical security of financial and medical facilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Josh Conway</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/josh_conway/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/josh_conway/</guid>
      <description>Josh Conway is a hacker, systems administrator, 3d printer software &amp;amp; hardware developer, amateur radio operator, musician, and more. He finds interest in creating new things, reusing tech in different ways, and abusing ‘unintended’ methodologies hidden inside hardware and software.
He is a member of BloomingLabs, the first hackerspace in Indiana, along with the cat-wrangler for the local 2600 meeting. Previous projects include: 3Dollar Scanner, Facial Recognition for your Con, and Thalmic Myo Open Sourcing via Public Hacking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Josh Turley</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/josh_turley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/josh_turley/</guid>
      <description>Josh Turley, Information Security Engineer, has been working in the IT space since the mid 2000’s. He has held thousands of jobs throughout hundreds of industries as they are related to Information Technology. He currently spends his days threat hunting and doing OSINT work for large organizations and penetration testing of both internal and 3rd party companies. He&amp;rsquo;s been known for his sarcastic tone and his heart of gold (the ship, not an actual heart of gold).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kathleen Smith</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/kathleen_smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/kathleen_smith/</guid>
      <description>Kathleen Smith, CMO aka Outreach Lead for CyberSecJobs.Com and ClearedJobs.Net, she has coached thousands of job seekers and employers on how to better connect and work together to achieve the mutual goal of employment. Kathleen presents at several security conferences each year on recruiting and job search. Some of the conferences she has presented at as a sole presenter or a moderator include BSidesLV, BSidesTampa, BSidesSATX, WIE IEEE, BSidesDE, FedCyber, Cyber912 and CyberSecureGov.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lisa Wallace</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/lisa_wallace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/lisa_wallace/</guid>
      <description>Lisa Wallace is MSI’s Technical Director and continues in her roles as security focal and project manager. Lisa is actively involved with internal and external vulnerability assessments and penetration testing, application assessments, digital forensics, threat intelligence, incident response and eDiscovery.
Her background over the last 20+ years includes the security items mentioned above, as well as server management and anti-virus research and administration. She has worked in a variety of fields, including utilities, financial services, and telecommunications and has consulted in a number of ancillary industries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Demarest</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/mark_demarest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/mark_demarest/</guid>
      <description>Mark Demarest is a security analyst for Bishop Fox, a consulting firm providing cybersecurity services to the Fortune 1000, global financial institutions.
Mark’s experience includes setting up multiple Cuckoo Sandboxes and aiding Bishop Fox consultants in examining payloads discovered during security assessments. While attending Arizona State University, he wrote a project report defending the need for companies to use Cuckoo Sandbox in their security programs. During the project, Mark guided a teammate without any experience in malware, malware sandboxes, or Linux command lines to set up his own Cuckoo Sandbox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mary Waddick</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/mary_waddick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/mary_waddick/</guid>
      <description>Mary Anne is a Cyber Engineer at Raytheon in Indianapolis. She has a master’s Degree in Information Assurance with a focus on Cyber Security from Regis University. She has worked at Raytheon for 29 years, both with Software Engineering and Cyber Engineering. She helps programs understand the importance of secure coding practices, and helps them use static code analysis tools for finding and understanding issues.
 talk Could Static Code Analysis and Secure Coding have Saved the Death Star?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Southworth</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/matthew_southworth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/matthew_southworth/</guid>
      <description>Matt is on the security team at Priceline. He was born in Indiana and somehow wound up near New York. More coffee, please.
 talk Behind The Locked Door: we built an escape room for security awareness  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micah Brown</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/micah_brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/micah_brown/</guid>
      <description>Micah K Brown is a member of the IT Security Engineering team at American Modern Insurance, part of the Munich RE Group. Over the past two years he has served as the lead Engineer on the DLP implementation for Data Loss Prevention for the Munich RE organizations located in North and South America. In this role Micah has learned the many intricacies of what works in a successful DLP project. In his free time, Micah serves on the Greater Cincinnati ISSA Chapter as Vice President.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike (Shecky Kavka</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/mike_shecky_kavka/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/mike_shecky_kavka/</guid>
      <description>Shecky (Mike) has been in the IT field for over 20 years. Having worked with computers since a young age, he currently is a Senior Network Engineer working on blue team solutions in the financial industry. He also is involved in the Chicago infosec community helping organize Burbsec North and the Chicago Infosec Happy hour. Shecky (Mike)
 talk Get off my lawn… or are we looking for the right people?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitchell Parker</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/mitchell_parker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/mitchell_parker/</guid>
      <description>Mitchell Parker is the Executive Director of Information Security and Compliance at Indiana University Health. Mitch’s areas of focus include taking complex security concepts and emerging technologies, and breaking them down so that everyone, even those who do not have security backgrounds, are able to understand and act upon them. He is a regular presenter at conferences include BSides, ISSA, HIMSS, ISMG Media, and numerous others. He also regularly writes for publications, and has a popular monthly blog with CSO Magazine, Security From the Upside Down, which covers technology, leadership, and communication issues in the Information Security community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mohammed Aldoub</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/mohammed_aldoub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/mohammed_aldoub/</guid>
      <description>Mohammed Aldoub is an independent security consultant from Kuwait, who, in his 10 years of experience, worked on creating Kuwait&amp;rsquo;s national infrastructure for PKI, cryptography, smartcards and authentication. Mohammed delivered security trainings, workshops and talks in the Netherlands, USA, Czech Republic, Lebanon, Riyadh, Kuwait, and other places.
Mohammed is deeply interested in malware, especially those used by state actors in the Middle East zone, where he volunteers as OWASP Kuwait&amp;rsquo;s chapter leader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nancy Snoke</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/nancy_snoke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/nancy_snoke/</guid>
      <description>Nancy Snoke is currently a Senior IT Security Engineer with PGAC specializing in application security. Previously, she has worked as penetration tester and as senior software engineer focusing on application security. Nancy has previously spoken at Bsides, Skydogcon, Derbycon and NOLACON. She got her undergraduate degree in Computer Engineering in New Orleans at Tulane University, and her Masters in Computer Science at University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign.
 talk One Random Insecure Wep Application Please (ORIWAP)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Priyank Nigam</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/priyank_nigam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/priyank_nigam/</guid>
      <description>As a senior security engineer, Priyank’s primary areas of focus are mobile application penetration testing and secure source code reviews. Over the past 4 years, he has advised Fortune 500 brands and startups and does mobile and IoT related research in his spare time. He also believes it is unwise to place trust in your smartphones.
 talk What The Frida Gave Me: A Novel Take on E-Ticket Forging and E-Ticket Stealing  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rebecca Deck</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/rebecca_deck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/rebecca_deck/</guid>
      <description>Rebecca Deck is a senior application security consultant for DirectDefense where she performs security testing on web, mobile, and client-side applications. Rebecca previously worked as a security engineer, incident responder, software developer, and soldier. Rebecca&amp;rsquo;s current work focuses on identifying software vulnerabilities, writing exploits, improving application testing methodologies, and better integrating software security in the software development life cycle.
 talk Of CORS it&amp;rsquo;s Exploitable! What&amp;rsquo;s Possible with Cross-Origin Resource Sharing?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rewanth Cool</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/rewanth_cool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/rewanth_cool/</guid>
      <description>Rewanth Cool is currently working as a security consultant at Payatu. Speaker at HITB Dubai, Null Pune and trainer at MIT Pune. He participates in numerous Capture-the-Flags (CTF) and enjoys participating in private bug bounty programs. He is a programmer and open source contributor. He is an active Hack The Box player as well.
Currently, he is focused on vulnerability research, web application security and contribution to security tools. He collaborated with Nmap maintainer Daniel Miller a.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rich Rumble</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/rich_rumble/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/rich_rumble/</guid>
      <description>Rich likes talking in the 3rd person, long walks on secure beaches. Rich likes soft LED lit dinners and has unrequited love for Bruce Schneier. Rich feels that last line made him sound creepy, but thinks anyone who takes the time to get to know Rich will understand. Rich has to know how things work and takes everything apart as soon as it arrives. Rich calls the re-assembly process &amp;ldquo;reenginering&amp;rdquo; because there are always items left over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ross Wolf</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/ross_wolf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/ross_wolf/</guid>
      <description>Ross Wolf is a researcher at Endgame where he creates solutions to simplify detecting adversarial behavior in endpoint data. Prior to Endgame, Ross was an engineer at MITRE where he led projects that automated blue team processes by creating graphs of process activity and grouping related alerts. He was recently co-granted a patent for CALDERA, a project which automated post-compromise adversary emulation by chaining together attacker techniques. Ross also contributed to ATT&amp;amp;CK and the Cyber Analytics Repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Holeman</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/ryan_holeman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/ryan_holeman/</guid>
      <description>Ryan Holeman resides in Austin Texas where he works as the Global Security Overlord on Atlassian&amp;rsquo;s Security team. He is also an advisor for the endpoint security software company Ziften Technologies. He received a Masters of Science in Software Engineering from Kent State University. His graduate research and masters thesis focused on C++ template metaprograming. He has spoken at many respected venues such as Black Hat, DEF CON, Lockdown, BSides, Ruxcon, Notacon, and Shmoocon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sam Crowther</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/sam_crowther/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/sam_crowther/</guid>
      <description>Sam Crowther is the CEO and founder of Kasada.io, starting the company at the age of 19. He now leads teams in Australia and the US, from his new base in Chicago. While still attending high school, Sam was the first student ever to be given two work placements at the &amp;ldquo;Australian NSA,&amp;rdquo; the Australian Signals Directorate. This experience allowed him quick placement on the Red Team at Macquarie Group, one of the world’s largest investment banks before leaving to dedicate his full efforts on leading Kasada’s efforts to destroy the Internet bot economy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secfarmer Secfarmer</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/secfarmer_secfarmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/secfarmer_secfarmer/</guid>
      <description>I dropped out of university because I thought it sucked. Now I do DFIR at cool companies.
 training Powershell 101 for Security Teams  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steven Bernstein</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/steven_bernstein/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/steven_bernstein/</guid>
      <description>@BSidesSATX coordinator. @BSidesLV AV Staff. IAM practitioner. #InfoSec #podcast host for @SEndeavors @CoderDojoSA Raspberry Pi class Working in the field of Digital Identity since 2002, SciaticNerd is actively involved in the San Antonio InfoSec community, attending and contributing to SAHA and other local groups and diligently working to promote involvement with computing, security, and technology.
 talk Cons &amp;amp; Careers  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Susan Sons</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/susan_sons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/susan_sons/</guid>
      <description>Susan Sons (sesons@iu.edu) is Chief Security Analyst at the Indiana University Center for Applied Cybersecurity Research (CACR), also serving as Information Security Officer for Open Science Grid and Deputy Director of the Research SOC. Her work focuses on secure software engineering, ICS/SCADA security, operational security practice for research and development organizations, and security for legacy technologies in high-stakes applications. For about 17 years, Susan has volunteered with Search and Rescue teams as a medic, field engineer, scene commander, and crisis communicator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swapnil Deshmukh</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/swapnil_deshmukh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/swapnil_deshmukh/</guid>
      <description>Swapnil Deshmukh is CTO &amp;amp; co-founder of Certus Cybersecurity Solutions LLC. Swapnil has more than a decade of experience in enterprise cybersecurity and leads technical delivery. Swapnil is a subject matter expert in the application, cloud and emerging technologies security domains. He is co-author of Hacking Exposed Series, a best practice security handbook, and a frequent contributor at conferences, roundtables and publications. Prior to Certus Cybersecurity, Swapnil served as a Senior Director on Visa Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tomer Hadad</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/tomer_hadad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/tomer_hadad/</guid>
      <description>I have been working in EY advanced cyber security center in Israel for the past three+ years. My role as the Subject Matter Expert of application security, includes performing vulnerability research, penetration testing and developing attack and penetration strategies for the following platforms and technologies: - Web applications, - Thick-Client/Native applications, - Mobile applications, - Multi-platforms products, including custom-made physical products, - Health care systems, - RFID systems. I have trained and developed tens of consultants, written training sessions and courses, and have developed tools and scripts in various fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tony Robinson</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/tony_robinson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/tony_robinson/</guid>
      <description>Tony Robinson is an NSM and Virtualization enthusiast out of southeast michigan. When hes not finding bad packets, building complex VM labs, or destroying malware, he can be found with his pet Bassett Hounds and wife, watching anime, or playing video games.
 training Building Virtual Labs: CCC Edition  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wendy Edwards</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/wendy_edwards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/wendy_edwards/</guid>
      <description>Wendy is a software developer interested in data science and security. She&amp;rsquo;s contributed to open source software projects and participated in NASA Datanauts and Space Apps Challenge. She was also a member of the 2017 SANS Women&amp;rsquo;s Academy, earned the GIAC GSEC, GCIH, and GCIA certificates, and joined the SANS Advisory Board.
 talk What Can Data Science Do for Security?  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wolfgang Goerlich</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/wolfgang_goerlich/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/wolfgang_goerlich/</guid>
      <description>J Wolfgang Goerlich supports information security initiatives for clients in the healthcare, education, financial services, and energy verticals. In his current role with CBI, a cyber security consultancy firm, Wolfgang is the senior vice president for strategic security programs. Wolfgang also sponsors the Academy teams, providing mentoring and guidance to the junior-level talent. He is an active part of the security community and hosts a YouTube video series. Wolfgang regularly advises on and presents on the topics of risk management, incident response, business continuity, secure development life cycles, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xena Olsen</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/xena_olsen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/xena_olsen/</guid>
      <description>Xena Olsen is a cyber threat intelligence analyst in the financial services industry. She is a graduate of the SANS Women’s Academy with 3 GIAC certifications and a current graduate student seeking an MBA in IT Management. Her current focus is malware analysis and paying it forward through her Women in Information Security Group.
 talk F! Attribution  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yashvier Kosaraju</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/yashvier_kosaraju/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/yashvier_kosaraju/</guid>
      <description>Yash is a Senior Security Engineer at Twilio.Prior to Twilio he was working to help secure Box. He has been working in security for over half a decade.working in a variety of roles ranging from consulting to enterprise product security teams. He is a seasoned speaker and has presented in BSides SLC 2016, BoxWorks 2016, HackMiami 2017, ,BSides San Diego 2018, and will be presenting at Troopers 2019
 talk Container Security Deep Dive  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yolonda Smith</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/yolonda_smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/yolonda_smith/</guid>
      <description>Yolonda Smith is a Lead Infosec Analyst with Target Corporation’s Business Information Security Office (BISO), aligned with the Digital portfolio. In this role, she provides expert security consultancy to developers, business leaders and key stakeholders to ensure that Target&amp;rsquo;s web and mobile applications are designed, developed and deployed with minimal risk to Target or its guests.
A security professional herself, she spent 8 years in the United States Air Force as a Cyberspace Operations Officer with duties and responsibilities varying from Mission Commander, (Advanced Network Operations) where her team planned and executed the first DoD Cyber Threat Hunting Missions to Flight Commander, (Cyber Defense Capabilities Development) where her team developed and fielded the first and only malware neutralization tool for the Predator Drone Weapon System.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zach Zenner</title>
      <link>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/zach_zenner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://circlecitycon.com/bios/zach_zenner/</guid>
      <description>I am a Cyber Security Analyst who does hobbyist research on the side. A lot of my research and proof of concepts are based on subjects I’ve heard on podcasts (or read about) and then create my own creative spin on the concept. Currently I have three certifications from various institutions revolving around cyber security and continue to work towards more as I shape my professional career.
 talk The Resilient Reddit C2  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>